DEAR X
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
- Thank you.
- Be careful.
I will. Thank you.
Are you all right, Mr. Choi?
Did you really ditch the shop
to go after that thief?
That was so brave.
Why do you keep going after
those guys?
- I'm fine. It was nothing.
- You should just become a cop.
Don't be so dramatic.
Go. I'm fine.
BASEBALL PRODIGY CHOI JUNG HO RETIRES
AFTER A STRING OF SETBACKS
FORMER BATTING TITLE CONTENDER
ANNOUNCES RETIREMENT
I sometimes look back
on those moments just before
she opened the gates of hell.
Was Ah Jin's encounter with that man
just a coincidence?
Or was it fate?
- I'll see you next week.
- Take care.
I start work next week.
Isn't it a little too soon
to start a part-time job?
I just want to clear my head
for a while.
I found you a place.
Here's the address and the door code.
It's too far from my school,
so I'll be staying with a friend.
- The place is empty, so you can...
- No.
I'm going back to my place.
But he knows where you live.
He'll come looking for you again
and ask for money.
I'm going to give him the money.
If I pay him regularly,
he won't beat me up.
That's the best I can do.
Bye.
You're moving out?
Why are you doing all this for her?
Get a grip, Jun Seo.
She's not part of your life anymore.
You're the one who did this.
You're the reason I can't let her go.
What did I do?
When her dad tried to do
those awful things
you went along with it.
After he went to prison
you threw her out on the streets
in the middle of winter.
You did that.
I did what I had to do.
I had to raise you.
I was trying to take care of you.
Stop making excuses.
You were just another abuser to her.
Jun Seo, don't do this to me.
Jun Seo.
Jun Seo, I can't live without you!
This is all because of her.
That devil.
EPISODE 3: BREAKING THE SHACKLES
We begin with our top story.
Random killings are on the rise
alongside a recent wave
of stalking-related crimes.
In Nojeong-dong,
a string of murder victims
were all found to have suffered
ongoing stalking before their deaths.
Now for the weekend forecast.
Most regions will see daytime highs
approaching 30 degrees
as the heat continues
through the week.
If you've finished, turn it in,
and you're free to go.
- Okay.
Did you see that girl at the cafe?
- Yes, I saw her.
- She's gorgeous.
I know, right? She's a knockout.
- Do you want to go see her?
- Do you?
- Are you down?
- Let's go.
Enjoy your drinks.
Excuse me. Do you have a boyfriend?
Yes, I do.
How about trading him for this guy?
- He's good-looking and he's tall.
- Stop it.
- Stand up. He's almost 190cm.
- Dude, what's wrong with you?
I'm really sorry,
but my boyfriend's better-looking.
I see.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let me know if you need anything.
Sure.
How many times
have you been hit on today?
All the customers are guys.
"Do you have a boyfriend?"
Oh, right.
Your photos are on social media.
They're all over the internet.
SHE'S LITERALLY FLAWLESS
I'M SO JEALOUS
SHE'D OUTSHINE LE NA IF SHE DEBUTED
WHY ISN'T SHE A CELEBRITY ALREADY?
SHE'S GORGEOUS
Do you remember her?
Wait, isn't she the one
who turned us down
when we tried to scout her
a few years ago?
That's right.
Here she is again.
It looks like
she's not with an agency yet.
Check again, just in case.
Aren't you worried about your photos
spreading online?
Should I ask them to take them down?
Just leave it.
It's good publicity for the cafe.
You're really pretty,
and you've got a great attitude.
No wonder Mr. Choi likes you.
By the way,
what is he always watching?
You don't know?
He was the legendary .400 hitter
and home run king.
One swing and it was over.
It was an automatic home run.
That's right.
"One swing and it was over"?
Yes.
He was huge back then.
What's he doing here, then?
Kwak Eun Hyeok
went for a reckless slide
and Mr. Choi broke his wrist
trying to tag him out.
Three surgeries
and a year of rehab later
he still couldn't make a comeback.
That was the end of his career.
He ended Mr. Choi's career,
but everyone still cheered for him.
If I were him,
I wouldn't be able to watch baseball.
You'd think so, right?
Proud of you, my friend. Good job.
He roots for the guy who ruined
his career and calls him a friend.
Who knows what he's thinking?
Welcome.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- I come bearing good news.
Who's that?
He's Im Seung Yong, CEO of PB Agency.
Just between us
Mr. Choi might be signing
a new contract.
I really hope he makes a comeback.
- You came a long way.
- Thank you.
He's a good man through and through.
Why do you think
I met someone like him
at this point in my life?
Maybe he's your guardian spirit.
- My guardian spirit?
- Yes.
Isn't it better to believe
guardian spirits exist?
If you think they're giving you
these trials for a greater purpose
it makes life a little easier.
If they really exist, like you said,
I wonder what their intention is.
Hello, this is Xanadu Coffee.
Did the girl working there
finish her shift?
Who's calling?
None of your business.
Can I get her number?
Excuse me.
You need to tell me
who you are first.
Also, I can't just give out
personal information...
Damn, what a lunatic.
Who was that?
Just another guy
asking for Ah Jin's number.
At least be polite
if you're going to ask.
Ah Jin.
Yoo Sik and I
will throw that out later.
You should go home.
It's getting late.
It's okay. I can do it.
What if you miss the last bus?
Sir, we're closed.
We're closed for the day.
But your sign is still lit.
Sorry. Please come back tomorrow.
We have to lock up soon.
But I want to see her.
Where's Ah Jin?
- Has she gone home yet?
- Well...
Sir, please step outside.
You can come back tomorrow.
Why are you pushing me?
- We have to close up now.
- Can you tell Ah Jin that...
Sorry, sir.
Please come again tomorrow morning.
Sorry about that.
Did you move out?
I only helped since I didn't want you
living with your mother.
Don't expect me
to keep supporting you.
When I die,
you won't get a single penny from me.
I understand.
Writers barely make any money.
How do you expect to make a living?
You still can't kill
a single ant, can you?
Every living creature
has a reason to live.
You sound just like him.
Did you just laugh?
I was just glad to hear
I take after my dad.
Who else would you take after?
JUN SEO
Ah Jin?
Ah Jin.
What took you so long?
Do you know
what almost happened to me?
Ah Jin.
Are you okay?
Shouldn't you see a doctor?
Are you hurt?
Jun Seo.
Yes.
How far would you go for me?
Answer me.
I'd do anything for you.
As long as it doesn't involve
killing someone
I'll do anything you ask me.
So you're letting your conscience
decide where the line is?
- That's not what I mean.
- Don't worry.
I never expected you
to go that far in the first place.
If you were brave enough
to kill a man for me
I'd have asked you
to start with Baek Seon Gyu.
You can kill anything
besides a man for me then, right?
Help...
Help me.
Please.
If you want to spare your life,
forget what happened tonight.
If you promise
to keep your mouth shut
I can call you an ambulance.
I won't say a word.
I promise.
There's a man injured
in the second alley
behind the Nojeong-gu townhouses.
It looks like a random assault.
He's losing a lot of blood.
Did you put the money
under the second flowerpot?
Hey.
She's easy on the eyes.
Get me a contact.
Put her in front of a camera
or ship her off to some island.
Just make sure it pays top dollar.
I might have to sell an organ
to pay off the interest.
I'm her father.
It's the least she can do for me.
I made that girl.
I brought her into this world.
She belongs to me.
I'll do whatever I want with her.
Got a problem with that?
Ah Jin.
What?
Were you going to push me off
this building?
Don't do anything stupid.
If you kill me, you'll be ostracized.
Your life will be over, you bitch.
You're pathetic.
I get you hate your old man,
but how dare you?
I can see right through you, bitch.
Next month, I want double the money.
Hey.
I'm saying this
out of old times' sake.
Stay away from that girl.
She's bad news.
Don't let her ruin your life, okay?
What did he do to you?
Jun Seo.
Can you hit me?
What?
It has to look like
a stalker attacked me.
Just hit me a few times.
No.
I can't do that.
I won't.
You won't?
Are you serious?
I should ask you that.
Are you seriously asking me
to hit you?
It's nothing new.
You've seen me get hit before.
That's exactly why I can't hit you.
It tore me apart,
and it still haunts me.
Fine.
I won't force you to do it.
Jun Seo.
I don't care if you get hurt
but I don't want to be the one
who hurts you.
I don't want to lose you.
You know I don't treat you
like I treat everyone else.
Ah Jin.
Sometimes, you scare me.
But I think it's because
you weren't loved growing up
so I don't know what to do.
Ah Jin.
I'll handle this.
Did something happen?
Pardon?
No, nothing happened.
It's just a little scratch.
You know you can tell me anything.
Don't bottle it up.
Believe it or not, I'm pretty strong.
I've never lost a fight before.
Okay?
You don't believe me?
I do.
I may be the boss
but you and Yoo Sik
are like family to me.
So whatever it is,
go ahead and use me, okay?
Use you?
That's right. Whatever it is.
But you're my boss.
That's what bosses are for.
Since Jun Seo has classes
late at night
I worry about you going home alone.
You said it's just you
and your father, right?
Yes, but my father lives far away.
I'd feel a lot more at ease
if your father lived close by.
What does he do?
He just works at a company.
He works the night shift.
WOMEN'S RESTROOM
Shit.
How much would we make
if we used an actress
instead of planting hidden cameras?
She's drop-dead gorgeous.
Yeah?
So I just need to drug her
and drop her off for a few hours?
Shit.
I found a hidden-camera offender.
I have proof, and I'm in pursuit.
You little punk!
If you hadn't called the cops
back then
I wouldn't have gone to prison!
My life is fucked up because of you!
Baek Ah Jin.
She's your daughter.
I brought her into this world,
so I'll do what I want with her.
Stay out of it.
She belongs to me
until the day she dies, you bastard.
Die!
Police! Step away!
You're under arrest for assault.
Sir, are you okay?
I think so.
Can you stand?
This way.
YEONGDONG POLICE STATION
So you two were step-siblings.
After your parents split up,
you kept stalking Baek Ah Jin.
And when her father found out,
you threatened to kill him?
Ah Jin.
Do you have proof
that he's been stalking you?
Text messages, perhaps?
A few days ago,
he was hiding at my place.
And he did this to me.
No, this man was the one
who did that to her.
He collects hidden-camera footage
from restrooms and gambles illegally.
I spoke with Detective Jin Dong Gyu
so I could hand over the evidence.
He did reach out to us.
So do you have the evidence?
I do.
It's on my phone.
Looking for this?
Show me the evidence.
You said it was on your phone.
Show me.
If you filed a false report,
the charges will be even heavier!
I'll be coming into some money soon.
I'll contact you,
so don't reach out to me until then.
You're not bluffing, right?
If I'm lying,
you can do whatever you want to me.
You've grown up. You really have.
Call me.
Damn it.
Detective.
May I have a moment with Jun Seo?
I'm afraid not.
It's against protocol for the victim
and the offender to have contact.
Before all this happened,
we were siblings.
I only need a minute. Please.
What are you doing?
If we go with your plan
and pin him as a petty offender
he'll be out in a few years.
It won't change a thing.
Don't be reckless.
You can't beat him.
I said I'd handle it.
You should've smashed his head
with that brick.
But you hesitated.
That's why you can't beat him.
So stay out of it.
Ah Jin.
Mr. Choi was
a professional athlete, right?
One swing and it was over.
It was an automatic home run.
"One swing and it was over"?
Don't do anything stupid.
If you kill me, you'll be ostracized.
You and Yoo Sik
are like family to me.
Whatever it is,
go ahead and use me, okay?
- Hey, Ah Jin.
- Good morning.
What happened to your face?
I fell.
You expect me to believe that?
That's not from a fall.
I'm okay.
Tell me the truth.
Who did this to you?
And that scratch on your neck.
Tell me what really happened.
Well...
The thing is...
I didn't say anything
because I didn't want you to worry.
But some guy has been following me
for a few days now.
We had a bit of a scuffle last night.
Did you call the police?
They said, unless he assaults me
or commits a crime
there's not much they can do
if the stalker denies it.
Jun Seo is staying with his grandpa
for a few days
so I am a little worried.
This won't do.
- Yoo Sik.
- Yes?
- Close up by yourself for now.
- What?
I'll take her home
for the time being.
- But...
- Thank you, Mr. Choi.
Take it.
What's this?
It's pepper spray. You might need it.
Thank you for looking out for me.
I hope you never have to use it.
Do you ever regret it?
Regret what?
Helping someone
when it isn't really your problem.
Sacrificing yourself for no gain.
Forgiving and rooting for the friend
who ruined your career.
I don't know.
Do I regret it?
Not really.
I'm not the type to dwell on regrets.
It's just how I am.
What if it backfires
and you end up hurting yourself?
I just follow my conscience.
I can't get anything done
when my conscience feels heavy.
Even if I end up getting hurt,
if that's the result of my choice
then so be it.
I hope you never change.
It's better for you that way.
You're a good person.
Hey, kiddo.
He's a good adult.
He's driven by justice
and willing to help others.
Is that a compliment?
He's the kind of adult
I need right now.
Thank you.
You live here alone?
I'll get you a studio near the cafe.
You should move.
You can't live here by yourself.
The rent might be higher,
but safety comes first.
That's a bit...
You don't need to worry
about the deposit.
Think of it as an advance
on your severance.
I appreciate your concern.
I'll think it over.
Okay.
Get home safely.
What's wrong? What is it?
Shoot.
What kind of psycho...
What's that?
YOU'RE NEXT
"You're next"?
Hey!
Ah Jin, go inside and lock the door.
Stop right there!
Stop!
What are you doing out here?
I told you to go inside
and lock the door.
You went after the stalker,
so I couldn't just sit still.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But I lost him.
It's getting late.
You should go home.
I can't leave you here alone.
Let me at least take you
to a sauna or...
I'm okay.
I already asked a friend
to come over.
Don't worry.
You should go. I'll head in too.
All right.
I left a bat by your door.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
Everything has its use.
Even small things, if used right,
can turn into an opportunity.
How about some beer
and fried chicken?
- I'm too full.
- What do you say?
Come on, let's go.
I need to buy cigarettes.
Where are you going?
Hey, it's Ah Jin.
Where do you think you're going?
- Wait, I know her.
- Let's hit the karaoke.
- I know her. Get off me.
- Let's go.
Come on.
- What are you doing?
- I'm not going home.
Hurry up.
Where's Ah Jin?
Has she gone home yet?
- Let's go!
- What's the holdup?
- Hurry up.
- I'm coming.
Let's go.
- What are you looking at?
- Hurry up.
I'll give you the money.
Be at my place by 8 p.m.
People only come to their senses
when they're scared.
"Fortune may turn into misfortune.
Tread carefully."
What the hell? How annoying.
Morning.
Ah Jin, someone's looking for you.
You know her?
Hello.
Ah Jin, are you sure
you don't want to give acting a try?
Why me?
Aren't there tons of people
desperate to be actors?
You were born with something
others don't have.
Be honest with me.
You have thought about it,
haven't you?
You're right. You've been on my mind.
But I can't right now.
I have to take care of something.
Can I ask you what that is?
It's a family matter.
If you're looking after
a sick family member, we can help.
No, it's something
I have to do myself.
Oh, well.
That's a shame.
But you seem set on your decision.
If you ever change your mind
promise you'll work with me,
not anyone else.
I'll treat you better
than any other agency.
I appreciate it.
All right, then. I'll see you around.
- Thank you for coming.
- Goodbye.
Should I get your autograph now?
I turned it down.
Why?
You'll be famous and rich.
What's not to like?
I just like the way it is now.
Jun Seo better watch out.
His girlfriend might become
a superstar.
Girlfriend? I'm not his girlfriend.
You're not? Then what's the deal?
Still no guardian?
Nothing happened last night, right?
I was too scared,
so I spent the night at my friend's.
But when I got home this morning,
my place was a mess.
I think someone broke in.
Does Jun Seo know about this?
I didn't want him to worry,
so I didn't tell him.
I'll tell him
when he gets back tomorrow.
I'm also thinking of moving.
- What about tonight?
- Tonight?
I'll have to manage.
Then...
Let's do this.
Sleep at my place tonight.
I'll sleep somewhere else.
I can stay at my parents' house.
No, it's okay.
You don't seem to get it.
This could be really dangerous.
Don't you have a meeting
with your agent tonight?
I do.
I'll go to my parents'
after the meeting.
So stay at my place tonight.
Jun Seo will be back tomorrow,
so just until then.
You should also reconsider moving
to a studio that's near the cafe.
I will, Mr. Choi.
It's raining cats and dogs out there.
In movies, bad things happen
when it rains like this.
You watch too many movies.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What is it?
I think I saw the stalker
in the beanie last night.
Where?
At a convenience store.
And he was with...
Who was he with?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I didn't sleep so well last night.
Wait here. I'll grab some ointment.
Didn't you say you had
a memorial service to get to?
Shouldn't you be on your way?
You're right. I should.
To Gudeok-dong?
Get in.
It's Building A, Unit 504.
I'll text you the door code.
Just punch that in and go inside.
Thank you.
Good luck with your meeting.
Text me if you need anything.
Okay.
Sir.
Could you take me to 13 Nojeong-dong
instead of Gudeok-dong?
Mr. Choi, I need to stop by my place
to grab a few things.
What? Right now?
Are you going to be okay?
I would have gone with you, then.
It'll only take a minute.
I just need to grab my wallet and ID.
Ask the driver to wait
in front of your place.
Call me if anything happens.
I thought you ran off.
You told me to be here at this time.
What took you so long?
You must be mad I kept you waiting.
You weren't the only one
who had to wait.
I've also been waiting
for this moment.
Cut the crap and give me the money.
I'll give you the money.
But can you put this on first?
What's this?
It's a gift.
Ever since I was little
I used to wonder
how nice it'd be if we got along
and had a good relationship.
Now that I'm earning money,
I wanted to get you something nice.
I'll give you the money,
so put this on.
It's your birthday gift, Dad.
You've lost your mind.
Calling me "Dad"?
What are you up to?
Just try it on.
It's not that difficult.
Just put it on for me.
If you do that,
I'll give you the money.
Did you put poison on this?
I'll put it on for you.
Dad.
You look so good.
It really suits you.
All right. I put it on.
Now, give me the money.
You've changed.
You used to be so spiteful.
Maybe you're finally growing up.
You need to toughen up.
You have to be ruthless to survive.
It's a cruel world out there.
It can turn on you in a second.
You crazy bitch.
Did you actually think
I'd give you the money?
You'll just take the money and leave.
But you know what?
I need you today, Dad.
Tell me. Do you want to kill me now?
If that's what you want,
I'll kill you.
You little...
Come here.
Did you have fun?
You should smile. This is fun, right?
Stand up.
- Hey, Ah Jin.
- I'm calling the police!
Go ahead. Call them.
- Help!
- Hello? Ah Jin?
Ah Jin...
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message...
YEONGDONG POLICE STATION
CALLING AH JIN
Get over here.
MR. CHOI
Shit.
- This is the police.
- There's been a break-in.
What's the address?
Nojeong-dong.
Are you near Nojeong Station?
No, not near the station.
Could you give me the exact address?
I don't know the exact address.
I have to endure this.
It takes ten minutes
to get here from the cafe.
I just need to hold on
for ten minutes.
Hey.
Hey...hey!
I won't let you die so easily.
I don't have the money in my hands.
Why did you have to piss me off?
Damn it.
What? Do you want some more of this?
I'll give you the money!
Shit.
Damn it!
Fuck.
Fucking bitch!
Do I have to break your hand
for you to be a good girl?
You were pretty
even when you were a baby.
Cry.
Wah.
Come on.
Cry for me.
That's it.
That's what I'm talking about!
Ah Jin wagered her life
in a gamble with God.
You crazy bastard! Get off her!
Ah Jin, are you okay?
Fuck you!
She's young enough
to be your daughter!
Ah Jin, are you all right?
Can you hear me?
Look at you.
You son of a bitch!
And in that wager
God took her side.
My dad...
Please come and help my dad.
He's bleeding so much.
My dad...
It's 13 Nojeong-dong, Nojeong-gu.
The rooftop house.
Please save my dad's life.
Please hurry.
And so, she offered up a sacrifice
and broke free from her shackles.
DEAR X
Subtitles by Ho Young Yun